[
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_SaatvikAgrawal01",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_01",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_01",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_04_SeeSpeaker",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_04_SeeSpeaker_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_FrancisTurner",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_04_SeeSpeaker_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_04_SeeSpeaker_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_04_SeeSpeaker_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_04_SeeSpeaker_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_04_SeeSpeaker_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_04_SeeSpeaker_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_04_SeeSpeaker_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_SaatvikAgrawal02",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_05",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_SaatvikAgrawal02",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_06",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva01",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_07",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_alt",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva01",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_07",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_success_alt",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva02",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_08",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva03",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_09",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva03",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_10",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_09",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_03",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_11",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_10",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower04",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_12",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_11",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_04",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_13",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_12",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower03",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_14",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_13",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower03",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_15",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_14",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_06",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_16",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_15",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower06",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_17",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_16",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower03",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_17",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_19_TalkToNewSpeaker",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_19_TalkToNewSpeaker_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_SaatvikAgrawal03",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_19",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_19_TalkToNewSpeaker_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_19_TalkToNewSpeaker_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_19_TalkToNewSpeaker_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_19_TalkToNewSpeaker_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_19_TalkToNewSpeaker_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_19_TalkToNewSpeaker_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_19_TalkToNewSpeaker_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_20_LostTribute",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_20_LostTribute_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower07",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_20",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_19",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_20_LostTribute_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_20_LostTribute_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_20_LostTribute_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_20_LostTribute_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_20_LostTribute_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_20_LostTribute_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_20_LostTribute_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 17,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower08",
  "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_20",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00",
  "AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_alt",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00",
  "AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_success_alt",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_title",
  "Description": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_FudeHinode",
  "AchievementId": "06A_B_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_15",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_title",
  "Description": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_RoyaHakimi02",
  "AchievementId": "06A_IR_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed_title",
  "Description": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_IR_02_GetSword",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_IR_02_GetSword_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_RoyaHakimi02",
  "AchievementId": "06A_IR_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_IR_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_IR_02_GetSword_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_IR_02_GetSword_title",
  "Description": "06A_IR_02_GetSword_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_IR_02_GetSword_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_IR_02_GetSword_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_IR_02_GetSword_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_IR_02_GetSword_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_GideonStormsbane02",
  "AchievementId": "06A_IR_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_IR_02 && 06A_MSQ_19",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_title",
  "Description": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_TalesaSerrano",
  "AchievementId": "06A_TS_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_success",
  "ObjectiveReward": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_title",
  "Description": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_ZhangHaoyu",
  "AchievementId": "06A_TS_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_TS_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_title",
  "Description": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_container",
  "AchievementId": "06A_TS_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_TS_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_title",
  "Description": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_F_01_CollectJam",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_F_01_CollectJam_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_KathrijnJanssen02",
  "AchievementId": "06A_F_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_10",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_F_01_CollectJam_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_F_01_CollectJam_title",
  "Description": "06A_F_01_CollectJam_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_F_01_CollectJam_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_F_01_CollectJam_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_F_01_CollectJam_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_F_01_CollectJam_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_KathrijnJanssen03",
  "AchievementId": "06A_F_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_F_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_title",
  "Description": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_T_01_DefeatPumas",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_T_01_DefeatPumas_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_TsuiFen",
  "AchievementId": "06A_T_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_15",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_T_01_DefeatPumas_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_T_01_DefeatPumas_title",
  "Description": "06A_T_01_DefeatPumas_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_T_01_DefeatPumas_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_T_01_DefeatPumas_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_T_01_DefeatPumas_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_T_01_DefeatPumas_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_TsuiFen",
  "AchievementId": "06A_T_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_T_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear_title",
  "Description": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_MichaelLewis03",
  "AchievementId": "06A_G_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_16",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_title",
  "Description": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_LionelDeLaRue02",
  "AchievementId": "06A_W_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_14",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns_title",
  "Description": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_MargotEmerson02",
  "AchievementId": "06A_Z_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_20",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_title",
  "Description": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_MargotEmerson01",
  "AchievementId": "06A_Z_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_title",
  "Description": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_ElricChapman",
  "AchievementId": "06A_S_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_title",
  "Description": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_ElricChapman",
  "AchievementId": "06A_S_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_Z_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_title",
  "Description": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_YelenaPajitnova01",
  "AchievementId": "06A_P_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_12",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools_title",
  "Description": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_YelenaPajitnova02",
  "AchievementId": "06A_P_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_P_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_title",
  "Description": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 25,
  "Task": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "06_YelenaPajitnova02",
  "AchievementId": "06A_P_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_P_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_title",
  "Description": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0623_0101_FQ01",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 5,
  "Task": "0623_0101_d_00_container_FQ01",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0623_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0623_0101_FQ01_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "0623_0101_FQ1_objective_title",
  "Description": "0623_0101_FQ1_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0623_0101_FQ1_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0623_0101_FQ1_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0623_0101_FQ1_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0623_0101_FQ1_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0623_0102_FQ02",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 10,
  "Task": "0623_0102_d_00_container_FQ02",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0423_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0623_0102_FQ02_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "0623_0102_FQ02_objective_title",
  "Description": "6023_0102_FQ02_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "6023_0102_FQ02_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "6023_0102_FQ02_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0623_0102_FQ02_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0623_0102_FQ02_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0423_0101_FQ03",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 15,
  "Task": "0423_0101_d_00_container_FQ03",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0923_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0423_0101_FQ03_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "0423_0101_FQ03_objective_title",
  "Description": "0423_0101_FQ03_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0423_0101_FQ03_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0423_0101_FQ03_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0423_0101_FQ03_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0423_0101_FQ03_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0923_0101_FQ04",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 20,
  "Task": "0923_0101_d_00_container_FQ04",
  "NpcDestinationId": "1223_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0923_0101_FQ04_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "0923_0101_FQ04_objective_title",
  "Description": "0923_0101_FQ04_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0923_0101_FQ04_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0923_0101_FQ04_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0923_0101_FQ04_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0923_0101_FQ04_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "1223_0101_FQ05",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 25,
  "Task": "1223_0101_d_00_container_FQ05",
  "NpcDestinationId": "1023_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_05",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "1223_0101_FQ05_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "1223_0101_FQ05_objective_title",
  "Description": "1223_0101_FQ05_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "1223_0101_FQ05_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "1223_0101_FQ05_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "1223_0101_FQ05_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "1223_0101_FQ05_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "1023_0101_FQ06",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 30,
  "Task": "1023_0101_d_00_container_FQ06",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0223a_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_06",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "1023_0101_FQ06_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "1023_0101_FQ06_objective_title",
  "Description": "1023_0101_FQ06_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "1023_0101_FQ06_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "1023_0101_FQ06_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "1023_0101_FQ06_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "1023_0101_FQ06_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0223_0101_FQ07",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 35,
  "Task": "0223_0101_d_00_container_FQ07",
  "NpcDestinationId": "1323_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_07",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0223_0101_FQ07_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "0223_0101_FQ07_objective_title",
  "Description": "0223_0101_FQ07_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0223_0101_FQ07_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0223_0101_FQ07_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0223_0101_FQ07_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0223_0101_FQ07_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "1323_0101_FQ08",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 40,
  "Task": "1323_0101_d_00_container_FQ08",
  "NpcDestinationId": "1523_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_08",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "1323_0101_FQ08_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "1323_0101_FQ08_objective_title",
  "Description": "1323_0101_FQ08_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "1323_0101_FQ08_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "1323_0101_FQ08_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "1323_0101_FQ08_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "1323_0101_FQ08_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "1523_0101_FQ09",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 40,
  "Task": "1523_0101_d_00_container_FQ09",
  "NpcDestinationId": "1123_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_09",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "1523_0101_FQ09_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "1523_0101_FQ09_objective_title",
  "Description": "1523_0101_FQ09_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "1523_0101_FQ09_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "1523_0101_FQ09_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "1523_0101_FQ09_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "1523_0101_FQ09_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "1123_0101_FQ10",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 45,
  "Task": "1123_0101_d_00_container_FQ10",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0324_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_10",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_09",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "1123_0101_FQ10_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "1123_0101_FQ10_objective_title",
  "Description": "1123_0101_FQ10_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "1123_0101_FQ10_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "1123_0101_FQ10_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "1123_0101_FQ10_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "1123_0101_FQ10_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "1424_0101_FQ11",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 50,
  "Task": "0324_0101_d_00_container_FQ12",
  "NpcDestinationId": "1424_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_11",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_10",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "1424_0101_FQ11_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "1424_0101_FQ11_objective_title",
  "Description": "1424_0101_FQ11_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "1424_0101_FQ11_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "1424_0101_FQ11_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "1424_0101_FQ11_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "1424_0101_FQ11_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0324_0101_FQ12",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 55,
  "Task": "1424_0101_d_00_container_FQ11",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0724_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_12",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_11",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0324_0101_FQ12_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "0324_0101_FQ12_objective_title",
  "Description": "0324_0101_FQ12_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0324_0101_FQ12_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0324_0101_FQ12_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0324_0101_FQ12_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0324_0101_FQ12_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0724_0101_FQ13",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "0724_0101_d_00_container_FQ13",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0823_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_13",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_12",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0724_0101_FQ13_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "0724_0101_FQ13_objective_title",
  "Description": "0724_0101_FQ13_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0724_0101_FQ13_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0724_0101_FQ13_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0724_0101_FQ13_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0724_0101_FQ13_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0823_0101_FQ14",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "0823_0101_d_00_container_FQ14",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0523_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_14",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_13",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0823_0101_FQ14_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "0823_0101_FQ14_objective_title",
  "Description": "0823_0101_FQ14_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0823_0101_FQ14_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0823_0101_FQ14_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0823_0101_FQ14_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0823_0101_FQ14_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0523_0101_FQ15",
  "Type": "SkillProgression",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "0523_0101_d_00_container_FQ15",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0523_Fisher",
  "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_15",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_14",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0523_0101_FQ15_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
  "Title": "0523_0101_FQ15_objective_title",
  "Description": "0523_0101_FQ15_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0523_0101_FQ15_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0523_0101_FQ15_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0523_0101_FQ15_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0523_0101_FQ15_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0699_0103_BarkimedesPup",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 25,
  "Task": "0699_0103_d_00_container_BarkimedesPup",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0699_Barkimedes",
  "AchievementId": "06_Quest_26",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_20 || 04A_Side02_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0699_0103_BarkimedesPup_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
  "Title": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_title",
  "Description": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0699_0101_Barkimedes",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 25,
  "Task": "0699_0101_d_00_container_Barkimedes",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0699_Barkimedes",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_26",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Repeatable": "TRUE",
  "Title": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_title",
  "Description": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "ScheduleId": "Daily"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 35,
  "Task": "0699_0102_d_00_container_Barkimedes2",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0699_Barkimedes",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Repeatable": "TRUE",
  "Title": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2_title",
  "Description": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2_complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "ScheduleId": "Daily"
 }
]